{"0": [{"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Health", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "What age group spend the most time sedentary in 2017?", "correct_answer": "Ages 60-79", "incorrect_answers": ["Ages 18-39", "Ages 6-11", "Ages 40-59"], "explanation": "Those ages 60-79 (also an age group filled with retirees) spent the most time sedentary (sitting or lying down).", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/t1/tbl1/en/tv.action?pid=1310033801"}}, {"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Health", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Please enter your height and weight. Do you think you are above or below the national average for BMI?", "correct_answer": "TRUE", "incorrect_answers": ["FALSE"], "explanation": "The national BMI (Body-Mass Index) is 26.25.", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/t1/tbl1/en/tv.action?pid=1310031901"}}], "1": [{"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Tourism", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "What was the most visited country by Canadians in 2018, excluding the United States?", "correct_answer": "Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["United Kingdom", "Kazakhstan", "Thailand"], "explanation": "It would seem Canadians love the sun! The top two destinations for travel in 2018 were Mexico, followed by Cuba. The United Kingdom was a distant third.", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/n1/daily-quotidien/190528/dq190528c-eng.htm"}}], "2": [{"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Geography", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "ON Region: What is the most populous CMA?", "correct_answer": "Toronto", "incorrect_answers": ["Ottawa-Gatineau", "Windsor", "Sudbury"], "explanation": "The most populous CMA in Ontario is the Greater Toronto Area, containing over 6.3 million individuals. Ottawa-Gatineau was a distant second with 1.4 million inhabitants.", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/t1/tbl1/en/tv.action?pid=1710013501"}}, {"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Geography", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "BC Region: What is the most populous CMA?", "correct_answer": "Vancouver", "incorrect_answers": ["Victoria", "Kelowna", "Abbotsford-Mission"], "explanation": "The most populous CMA in BC is Vancouver, containing 2.6 million individuals. Victoria was a distant second with around 400,000 inhabitants.", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/t1/tbl1/en/tv.action?pid=1710013501"}}, {"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Geography", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "QC Region: What is the most populous CMA?", "correct_answer": "Montreal", "incorrect_answers": ["Ottawa-Gatineau", "Quebec", "Sherbrooke"], "explanation": "The most populous CMA in Quebec is Montreal, containing over 4.6 million individuals. Ottawa-Gatineau was a distant second with 1.4 million inhabitants.", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/t1/tbl1/en/tv.action?pid=1710013501"}}, {"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Geography", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "How many times can Canada's road network circle the equator", "correct_answer": "19", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "0", "52"], "explanation": "Yep, we've got a lot of roads. It's a big country.", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/n1/daily-quotidien/180824/dq180824a-eng.htm"}}], "3": [{"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Cannabis", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Which province had the highest percentage of cannabis users in the first quarter of 2019?", "correct_answer": "Alberta", "incorrect_answers": ["Ontario", "Quebec", "British-Columbia"], "explanation": "21.5% of inhabitants in Alberta had used Cannabis, edging out Ontario (20%) for the top spot.", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/n1/pub/13-610-x/cannabis-eng.htm"}}, {"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Cannabis", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The GDP of the Medical Cannabis Industry grew by less than 10% after legalization. TRUE or FALSE.", "correct_answer": "FALSE", "incorrect_answers": ["TRUE"], "explanation": "The Medical Cannabis Industry grew by well over 10% after legalization, between 2017 and 2018. The 2017 GDP was $102 million, and the 2018 GDP was $1.6 billion. What a difference a year makes!", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/t1/tbl1/en/tv.action?pid=3610060101"}}], "4": [{"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Agriculture and Nature", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "True or false: More than 60% of food bought by Canadians is produced domestically.", "correct_answer": "TRUE", "incorrect_answers": ["FALSE"], "explanation": "The answer is true! Seventy percent of food purchased in Canada was from Canadian sources.", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/n1/en/catalogue/16-201-X"}}, {"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Agriculture and Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "How much of Canada's Forest Lands are protected?", "correct_answer": "7%", "incorrect_answers": ["0%", "50%", "99%"], "explanation": "240,410 kilometres squared of Canadian Forest were protected in 2006.", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/n1/en/catalogue/16-201-X"}}, {"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Agriculture and Nature", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "What is the deepest lake in Canada?", "correct_answer": "Great Slave Lake", "incorrect_answers": ["Lake Erie", "Lake Winnipeg", "Lake Mazinaw"], "explanation": "Great Slave Lake is 614 metres deep! This is the southern of two major lakes in the Northwest Territories, the lake to the north being Great Bear Lake.", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/n1/en/catalogue/16-201-X"}}], "5": [{"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Data Literacy", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Self-reported physical activity for 12-17 year olds was 78.2 minutes per day. Is this number greater than the actual measured amount?", "correct_answer": "TRUE", "incorrect_answers": ["FALSE"], "explanation": "FALSE: Self-reported vigorous physical activity for 12-17 year olds was 78.2 minutes. Activity monitors found this was an over-estimation, with actual physical activity at an average of 49.7 minutes per day.", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/n1/pub/82-003-x/2019007/article/00001-eng.htm"}}, {"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Data Literacy", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "A survey that covers a group of people over a long period of time, with check-ins at pre-defined times, is a longitudinal survey. TRUE of FALSE.", "correct_answer": "TRUE", "incorrect_answers": ["FALSE"], "explanation": "Longitudinal surveys study a certain group of people over an extended period of time. Some examples include Statistics Canada's Labout Force Survey, which asks participants questions over a 6-month span.", "link": "https://www150.statcan.gc.ca/n1/en/catalogue/71-543-G"}}, {"Response_Code": 0, "Results": {"category": "Data Literacy", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Canadian Community Heal Survey, which asks certain Canadians from different areas about their health, is an example of a Census. TRUE or FALSE.", "correct_answer": "FALSE", "incorrect_answers": ["TRUE"], "explanation": "A Census is a study which covers an entire population. For example, the Census of Canada is conducted every 5 years, and asks every Canadian about their lives. The Canadian Community Health Survey is a sample survey, meaning only some people of the entire population are asked questions.", "link": "http://www23.statcan.gc.ca/imdb/p2SV.pl?Function=getSurvey&SDDS=3901"}}]}